Guide to the Wilmarth Sheldon Lewis Papers
The Lewis Walpole Library
- Correspondence, 1901–1979; Series I; 76.56; 181 boxes
  - General Correspondence
    - Dunham, William Huse, 1901-1982, 1940–1968 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Dunn, James C. (James Clement), 1890-1979, 1945–1961 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Dunning, Patrick J., 1963–1976 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Du Pont, Henry Francis, 1880-1969, 1949–1967 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Du Prey, Pierre de la Ruffinière, 1962–1966 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Durham, James Andrew Cuninghame, 1933–1949 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Durlacher Bros., 1947–1960 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Duryee, Samuel S., 1967 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Du Tant, Charles, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Dwyer, William E., 1973–1979 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Dyer, Thomas C., 1960–1963 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Ea-Ez, general (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - E. L. Hildreth & Company, 1936–1949 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - E. M. Lawson & Company, 1939–1978 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - E. Mathews (Firm), 1925–1963 (Box 37, Folder 11-12)
    - E. P. Goldschmidt & Co., 1945–1962 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - E. Parsons & Sons, 1929–1933 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - E. Seligmann, 1952–1953 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - E. Weyhe, Inc., 1937–1968 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Early, Benjamin, 1942–1949 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Eaton, Andrew Jackson, 1914-, 1954–1960 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Eaton, Peter, 1914-1993, 1959–1960 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Ecklund, John E., 1916-2000, 1967–1974 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Eddy, George Simpson, 1936–1941 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Edgar H. Wells & Co., 1928–1941 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Edgcumbe, John, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Edinburgh University Library, 1934–1979 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Edmonds, Iris, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Edmunds, Andrew, 1975–1977 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Educational Testing Service, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Edward Eberstadt & Sons, 1951–1973 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Edward L. Eyre & Co., 1935–1978 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Edwards, Arthur T., 1951 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Edwards, H. W., 1951–1969 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Edwards, Ralph, 1952–1962 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Egan, J. K., 1950–1955 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Ehrman, John, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Eicks, Clement S., 1954 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Eidelberg, Martin P., 1967–1969 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Eleutherian Mills Historical Library, 1956–1973 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Eliot, George Edwin, 1864-, 1932–1943 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Elkins, William McIntire, 1882-1947, 1938–1941 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Eller, Ernest M., 1903-1992, 1964–1967 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Eliot's Bookstore, 1976–1977 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Elmore, Edmundo, 1973–1979 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Emily Driscoll (Firm), 1950–1966 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Enders, Allie, 1966–1971 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Enders, Ostrom, 1956–1978 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Engel, Claire Eliane, 1937–1947 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Engley, Donald B. (Donald Brown), 1919-2012, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - English-Speaking Union, 1947–1979 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Epworth, Lincoln, 1966–1973 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Erskine, David, 1934–1975 (Box 39, Folder 1-2)
    - Erving, Selma, 1954–1958 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Esdaile, Arundell James Kennedy, 1880-1956, 1929–1952 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Eshleman, Dorothy H., 1954 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Essex Institute, 1951–1973 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Essex Record Office, 1951–1976 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Eton College, 1939–1958 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Evarts, Effingham, 1938-1939, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Ewen, Barbara, 1943–1947 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Exeter, Diana Henderson Cecil, Marchioness of, 1911-1982, 1948–1965 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Export Book Co., 1963–1972 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Eyre, Dean Atherton, 1947–1978 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Fa-Fl, general (Box 39, Folder 14-15)
    - Fo-Fz, general (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - F.H. Swift (Firm), 1925–1971 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - F. R. Meatyard (Firm), 1937 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Fagan, Thomas C. M., 1964–1967 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Falkner Grierson & Co. Ltd., 1977–1978 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Fallen, Helene, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Farmington High School Library Club, 1961–1974 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Farmington Town Council, 1950–1951 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Farmington Volunteer Fire Department, 1964–1976 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Farmington War Memorial Committee
      - Correspondence and photographs, 1966–1970 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Designs by John Howard Benson, 1969 November 25 (Box 336 (Oversize), Folder 2)
        Designs for war memorials for Farmington and Unionville, Connecticut, cut at the John Stevens Shop, Newport.
    - Farmington Land Trust, Inc., 1976 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Farnam, Thomas W., 1933–1941 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Farrar, John Chipman, 1896-1974, 1936–1955 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Farwell, John Villiers and Margaret W., 1946–1978 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Feisenberger & Gurney Ltd., 1951–1952 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Feiss, Carl, 1952–1953 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Fergusson, James, Sir, 1904-1973, 1952–1972 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Feuillerat, Albert, 1874-1953, 1935–1951 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Field, Alan, 1952–1970 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Fierro, Bess, 1967–1976 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Finberg, Hilda, 1937–1952 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Fine Arts Appraisal Corporation, 1940–1962 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Fink, Frances Sharf, 1951–1954 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Finkel, Charlotte, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Finlay, Susan, 1970–1971 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Finley, David E. (David Edward), 1946–1976 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Fischer, Edwin Garvin, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Fisher, Barbara Colomb, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Fisher, Harry, 1957–1964 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Fisher, Samuel H. (Samuel Herbert), 1867-1957, 1937–1949 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Fitts, Clive Hamilton, 1900-1984, 1948–1979 (Box 42, Folder 1-2)
    - Fitzherbert, Nicholas H., 1953–1956 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Fitz-patrick, Denys, 1935–1961 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Fitzwilliam Museum, 1935–1979 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Flandrau, Grace, 1889-1971, 1944–1971 (Box 42, Folder 6-7)
    - Fleming, Ethel, 1943–1948 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Fleming, John F. (John Francis), 1910-, 1952–1971 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Fleming, Lindsay, 1949–1965 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Flenniken, Clarissa, 1955–1979 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Fletcher, H. M., 1958–1964 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Fletcher, Ifan Kyrle, 1905-1969, 1931–1969 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Flew, Henrietta L., 1952 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Flink, Stanley, 1973–1977 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Flint, Alberta M., 1961–1975 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Flower, Robin, 1881-1946, 1935–1944 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Flynn, Ada E., 1976–1977 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Flynt, Henry N. (Henry Needham), 1893-1970, and Henry N., Jr., 1952–1972 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Folger Shakespeare Library, 1934–1974 (Box 43, Folder 12-13)
    - Folio Society (London, England), 1949–1964 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Follett, Wilson, 1887-1963, and Helen, 1920–1969 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Fontanne, Lynn, 1966–1968 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Foord, Archibald S., 1954–1966 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Forbes, William A., 1938–1975 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Ford, Brinsley, 1954–1977 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Ford, Herbert, 1950 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Forman, Benno M., 1977 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Forman, Kenneth, 1925-, 1968–1979 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Forrest, Edward, 1950–1964 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Forrest, John R., 1950–1952 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Forster, Eleanor, 1959–1961 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Fosburgh, Minnie Astor and James, 1956–1958 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Foster, Allen Evarts, 1885-1969, 1937–1965 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Foxon, David F. (David Fairweather), 1960–1967 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Francis Collin Ltd., 1965 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Francis Edwards (Firm), 1924–1966 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Frank Hammond (Firm), 1949–1968 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Frankfurter, Felix, 1882-1965, 1942–1955 (Box 45, Folder 1-5)
    - Frankfurter, Felix, 1882-1965, 1956–1978 (Box 46, Folder 1-4)
    - Franklin, Colin and Charlotte, 1971–1975 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Frantz, Peter B., 1972 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Fredk. B. Daniell & Son, 1962–1970 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Free Library of Philadelphia, 1956–1959 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Freedley, Mary, 1940–1948 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Freehafer, John, 1965–1968 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Freemantle, Anne, 1944–1967 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Frégnac, Claude, 1965–1969 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - French & Company (New York, N. Y.), 1935–1948 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - French & Spanish Book Corporation, 1937–1944 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Freund, Paul A. (Paul Abraham), 1908-1992, 1958–1961 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Frick Art Reference Library, 1937–1951 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Frick Collection, 1950–1973 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Frost, Jack, 1974–1975 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Frost, Joseph W. P., 1971–1974 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Fry, Clements Collard, 1892-1955, 1938–1951 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Fuller, Constance Greenough, 1961 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Fulton, Darrow B., 1939–1940 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Fulton, John F. (John Farquhar), 1899-1960, 1934–1977 (Box 47, Folder 12-13)
    - Fulton, William Shirley, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Funston, G. Keith, 1910-1992, 1950–1951 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Furniss, Edgar S. (Edgar Stevenson), 1890-1972, 1934–1967 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Fussell, Paul, 1924-2012, 1959–1960 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Ga-Gz, general (Box 48, Folder 1-3)
    - G. A. Baker & Co. Gallery, 1939–1940 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - G. F. Sims (Rare Books), 1955–1968 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - G. Heywood Hill, Ltd., 1952–1978 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Gabriel, Ralph Henry, 1890-1987, 1938–1947 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Gaddis, Eugene R., 1947-, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Gaeta, Sebastian, 1977–1979 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Gage, Charles S., 1956–1964 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Gaines, Peter, 1973–1975 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Gallagher de Parks, Mercedes, 1883-, 1943–1950 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Galloway, Philippa Fendall Stewart, Countess of (-1974), 1958 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Gander & White Ltd., 1936–1960 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Garland Publishing, Inc., 1974–1978 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Garlick, Kenneth, 1916-2009, 1961–1973 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Garrett, Maria Clewes, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Garrett, Wendell D., 1960–1974 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Garrison, Lloyd K. (Lloyd Kirkham), 1897-1991, 1952–1977 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Garstin, Betty, 1946–1966 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Garvan, Anthony N. B., 1948–1961 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Gaskell, Constance Milnes, 1885-1964, 1952–1961 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Gaskell, Philip, 1951–1970 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Gaskill, Francis, 1930–1946 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Gates, Alice, 1959–1962 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Gault, Margaret, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Gearing, Ernest G., 1978–1979 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Geier, Frederick V., 1965–1972 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Gemmett, Robert J., 1967–1977 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - General Trading Company, 1957 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - George, M. Dorothy (Mary Dorothy), 1957–1961 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - George, George B., 1953 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - George, Graham, 1912-1993, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - George Hotel (Edinburgh, Scotland), 1955–1957 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Gerould, James Thayer, 1872-1951, 1934–1935 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Giamatti, A. Bartlett, 1977–1978 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Gibson, Jeremy Sumner Wycherley, 1974–1977 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Gibson, Langhorne, 1899-, 1926–1969 (Box 49, Folder 21-22)
    - Gibson, Langhorne, 1899-, 1969–1979 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Gifford, Jack and Barbara, 1969–1976 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Gifford, John A., 1941–1977 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Gilbertson, Mary Steward, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Gilcher, Edwin, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Gill, Brendan, 1914-1997, 1961–1971 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Gilpin's Lunch, 1932–1979 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Ginsburg, Benjamin, 1972–1976 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Glasgow Art Gallery and Museum, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Glebe House & Gallery, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Glencross, R. M., 1935–1941 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Glick, William J., 1979 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Glidden, Anna ("Nannie") Dale Biddle Burgess, 1960–1976 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Glidden, H. Spencer, 1961–1964 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Glixon, David M., 1973–1974 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Godfrey, Thomas C., 1922–1923 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Goff, Frederick Richmond, 1916-1982, 1945–1976 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Golden, John, 1932–1951 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Gooch, Bryan N. S., 1968 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Goodenough, Erwin Ramsdell, 1893-1965, 1938–1948 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Goodhart, Arthur L. (Arthur Lehman), 1891-1978, 1946–1965 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Goodison, Jack Weatherburn, 1955–1965 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Goodman, Doris, 1963–1971 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Goodspeed, Edgar J. (Edgar Johnson), 1871-1962, 1952–1953 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Goodspeed Opera House, 1959–1966 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop (Boston, Mass.), 1932–1977 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Goodwin, Francis, 1895-1976, and Jacqueline, 1939–1976 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Goodwin, Philip Lippincott, 1885-1958, 1939–1951 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Goodwin, Susan, 1974–1979 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Goodwin, Tulie, 1967–1979 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Goodyear, A. Conger (Anson Conger), 1877-1964, 1949–1963 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Gordan, Phyllis Walter Goodhart, 1962–1966 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Gould, Erl C. B., 1944–1963 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Gould, Frank E., 1958–1960 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Graham, Fred W. W., 1939–1968 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Graham, Frank Porter, 1886-1972, 1953–1967 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Grafton & Co., 1924–1952 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Gran, Anthony, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Granbery, Carleton, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Grant, Keith, 1930-, 1974–1976 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Grant, Maurice Harold, 1872-, 1937–1943 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Great Britain. Parliament. House of Commons. Library, 1953–1969 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Great Britain. Public Record Office, 1936–1971 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Great Britain. Royal Commission on Historical Manuscripts, 1967–1970 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Green, Rosalie, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Greene, A. Crawford and Natalie, 1938–1967 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Greene, James C., 1957–1958 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Greenfield, Arthur, 1965–1973 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Greenough, William, 1938–1952 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Greenway, John S., 1960–1975 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Gregg Press, 1963–1964 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Gregory, George, 1923–1957 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Gregory, Katharine, 1937–1938 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Griffin, Gillett G. (Gillett Good), 1928-2016, 1954 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Griffith, R. M., 1946–1957 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Griffith, Samuel B., 1975–1977 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Grimshaw Gallery, 1974–1978 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Grimwade, Russell, 1879-1955, 1947–1958 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Grinke, Paul, 1966–1977 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Griswold, Alfred Whitney, 1906-1963, 1945–1954 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Griswold, Alfred Whitney, 1906-1963, 1954–1956 (Box 53, Folder 1-2)
    - Griswold, Mary B., 1973–1979 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Grocki, John and Jean, 1960–1970 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Grocki, Michael and Helen, 1951–1958 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Grolier Club, 1936–1976 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Grosvenor, Theodore Phinney and Anita, 1964–1971 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Grothe, Irma S., 1953 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Groton, Anngenette, 1955–1972 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Groton School, 1941 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Grummon, Robert M. and Louise, 1950–1972 (Box 54, Folder 1-2)
    - Grundy, Isobel, 1968–1971 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Guelker, Francis T., 1969–1979 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Guildford Museum, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Gunmere, Richard and Christine, 1950–1960 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Gunther, Helen, 1967–1976 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Guy, Frances, 1978–1979 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Ha-Han, general (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Har-Hz, general (Box 55, Folder 1-3)
    - H. Michaelyan, Inc., 1950 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - H. D. Lyon (Firm), 1952–1976 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - H. P. Kraus (Firm), 1946–1974 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - H. W. Brettell, Ltd., 1970–1979 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - H. W. Pratley (Firm), 1947–1965 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Hackenbroch, Yvonne, 1952–1955 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Hadley, Morris, 1894-, 1940–1975 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Hadley, Rollin van N., 1970–1973 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Haight, Gordon Sherman, 1953–1974 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Hake, Henry, 1892-1951, and Patricia, 1927–1953 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Hale, Richard Walden, 1909-1976, 1934–1966 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Hale, Robert, 1889-1976, 1970–1974 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Hall, Clayton Morris, 1896-, 1950–1971 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Hall, H. Gaston, 1960–1975 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Halliday, Bernard, 1937–1959 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Halliday, W. R. (William Reginald), 1886-1966, 1953 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Halsband, Robert, 1914-1989, 1937–1977 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Ham House Survey, 1934–1948 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Hamburger, Joseph, 1922-, 1962–1977 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Hamill & Barker, 1937–1970 (Box 56, Folder 15-16)
    - Hamilton, Chauncey, 1946 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Hamilton, Colin H., 1971–1979 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Hamilton, George H., 1937–1968 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Hamlin, Cyrus, 1959–1962 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Hamlin, Hannibal, 1958–1977 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Hamlin, Margaret, 1965–1978 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Hammelmann, Hanns, 1954–1969 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Hammond, Dorothy P., 1965–1966 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Hammond, Mason, 1903-2002, 1954–1965 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Hamond, Anthony, 1933–1977 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Hanbury-Williams, John, Sir, 1940–1941 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Hand, Learned, 1872-1961, 1941–1970 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Hanes, John Wesley, 1925-, 1954–1960 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Hanes, Ralph P. and Dewitt, 1963–1979 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Hanke, Lewis and Kate, 1942–1978 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Hanley, Miles L., 1940–1941 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Hanna, L. C., Jr. (Leonard Colton), 1889-1957, 1938–1968 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Hanson, Lawrence, 1941–1952 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Hanson, T. W., 1954–1955 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Harcourt, William Edward, 1908-1979, and Elizabeth, 1935–1976 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Harfst, Betsy Perteit, 1963–1968 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Harkness, Edward Stephen, 1874-1940, 1936 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Harkness, Hope, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Harmsworth, R. Leicester (Robert Leicester), Sir, 1870-1937, 1934–1953 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Harper, Francis C., 1938–1952 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Harper & Brothers, 1925–1960 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Harper & Row, Publishers, 1971–1977 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Harrah, Edward, 1938–1939 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Harrington, Karl Pomeroy, 1861-1953, 1950 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Harris, John, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Harris, Kitty Webb, 1975–1979 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Harrison, P. L., 1960–1977 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Harrod, Wilhelmine Cresswell, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Harte, Charles Rufus, 1870-1956, 1938–1941 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Hartwell, Shattuck W. (Shattuck Wellman), 1928-, 1969–1975 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Harvard Law School. Library, 1967 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Harvard University Library, 1933–1979 (Box 58, Folder 18-19)
    - Haskins, Caryl P. (Caryl Parker), 1908-2001, 1963–1971 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Hastings, Robert P. (Robert Pusey), 1910-1996, 1952–1979 (Box 59, Folder 2-4)
    - Hatfield, Frank W., 1917-, 1944 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Hatton, Ragnhild Marie, 1939–1957 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Hawks, Stanley, 1954–1961 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Hawthorne, W. R. (William R.), 1973–1974 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Hay-Adams Hotel, 1958–1959 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Haydock, Doris, 1958–1979 (Box 59, Folder 10-11)
    - Hayes, Richard J., 1902-, 1950–1956 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Hayward, John, 1905-1965, 1935–1965 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Hazell, Thomas A., 1972–1974 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Hazen, Allen T. (Allen Tracy), 1904-, 1934–1956 (Box 60, Folder 4-7)
    - Hazen, Allen T. (Allen Tracy), 1904-, 1957–1973 (Box 61, Folder 1-4)
    - Hazen, Allen T. (Allen Tracy), 1904-, 1974–1977 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Heal, Ambrose, 1872-1959, 1937–1948 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Heath, Martin, 1971–1977 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Heath, Roland, 1950–1971 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Heche, Carol, 1962–1977 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Heckscher, August, 1913-1997, 1951–1973 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Heffelfinger, F. Peavey, 1952–1977 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Heim Gallery, 1975–1976 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Hellman, Geoffrey T. (Geoffrey Theodore), 1907-1977, 1948–1973 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Heminway, J. Callender, 1975–1978 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Hemlow, Joyce, 1965–1973 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Henderson, Priscilla A. B., 1961–1962 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Henning, Basil Duke and Alison, 1953–1973 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Henry, Barklie McKee, 1902-1966, 1958–1963 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery, 1934–1979 (Box 62, Folder 15-16)
    - Henry Naylor (Firm), 1951–1957 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Henry Sotheran Ltd., 1944–1979 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Henry Stevens, Son & Stiles, 1938–1955 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Herbert Reichner, Inc., 1939–1958 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Herring, Edmund, Sir, 1892-, 1947–1974 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Hertford, Hugh Edward Conway Seymour, Marquess of, 1930-1997, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Hertfordshire County Record Office, 1950–1957 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Hewes, James E. and Lydia, 1942–1968 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Hewes, Philip and Mary, 1965–1979 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Hexter, J. H. (Jack H.), 1910-1996, 1977 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Heygate, William, Sir, 1933–1948 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Hicks, David, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Hill, Draper, 1962–1975 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Hill, Harold, 1960–1963 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Hill, J. Jewill, 1938 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Hill, Patrick and Ginny, 1959–1979 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Hill, Walter M. (Walter Martin), 1868-, 1933–1941 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Hilles, Frederick W. (Frederick Whiley), 1900-1975, 1933–1975 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Hill-Stead Museum, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Hinkle, Beatrice M., 1939–1957 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Hinks, John M., 1947–1963 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Historical Society of Fort Washington (Fort Washington, Pa.), 1971 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - History Today, Inc., 1954–1968 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Hitchcock, Henry-Russell, 1903-1987, 1949–1963 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Hobart and William Smith Colleges, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Hochschild, Harold K., 1892-1981, and Mary, 1958–1969 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Hodgart, Matthew John Caldwell, 1962–1963 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Hodges, Elizabeth Jamison, 1961–1975 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Hodgson & Co., 1935–1955 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Hofer, Philip, 1898-1984, 1933–1974 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Hoffecker, Douglas M. (Douglas Meade), 1951–1953 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Hofmann & Freeman Antiquarian Booksellers, 1969–1978 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Hogan, Charles Beecher, 1906-, 1937–1979 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Holden, Reuben A. (Reuben Andrus), 1918-, 1947–1978 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Holden, Robert F., 1896?-1944, 1928–1944 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Holden, Theodore, 1951 (Box 64, Folder 17)